[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The national motto of the Republic of Botswana is Pula. What does this mean in English?", "correct_answer": "Rain", "incorrect_answers": ["Strength", "Wisdom", "Sunshine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "No dinosaur fossils have been found on which one of these continents?", "correct_answer": "None of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Antarctica", "Europe", "Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a tuque?", "correct_answer": "A winter hat typically worn in Canada.", "incorrect_answers": ["A type of bikini that became very popular around 2004.", "A type of winter snow that falls horizontally in very high latitudes.", "A type of fruit that used to be called a winter peach"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie G-Force, what kind of animal is secret agent Mooch?", "correct_answer": "Fly", "incorrect_answers": ["Bee", "Hummingbird", "Flea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This ancient thinker, who was the first person to propose a heliocentric model of the Solar system,  considered that the Earth revolves around the Sun.", "correct_answer": "Aristarchus", "incorrect_answers": ["Aristades", "Hippachus", "Heron"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 20-kilometre artificial island, situated in the river Danube, was nicknamed the Copa Kagrana?", "correct_answer": "Donauinsel", "incorrect_answers": ["Peberholm", "Burj al-Arab", "Odaiba"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This strongly acidic and detoxifying fruit grows on trees named Citrus sinensis and Citrus aurantium.", "correct_answer": "Orange", "incorrect_answers": ["Grapefruit", "Avocado", "Lemon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sean Connery starred as William of Baskerville in this 1986 movie based on a famous novel by Umberto Eco.", "correct_answer": "The Name of the Rose", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bomb and the General", "Foucaults Pendulum", "The Island of the Day Before"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which song did Randy Travis perform for the Black Dog soundtrack?", "correct_answer": "My Greatest Fear", "incorrect_answers": ["Road Man", "Nowhere Road", "I Wanna Remember This"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is true about the human blood plasma?", "correct_answer": "It comprises 55% of the blood content.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is colorless.", "All of these", "It contains 60% water."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What celebrity couple starred in Stanley Kubricks 1999 neo-noir psychological thriller movie Eyes Wide Shut?", "correct_answer": "Tom Cruise and Nicole Kidman", "incorrect_answers": ["Brad Pitt and Gwyneth Paltrow", "Brad Pitt and Jennifer Aniston", "Tom Cruise and Penelope Cruz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mel Gibson starred in the movie Mad Max released in 1981.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]